Marissa: And you know what's something, this
might be off cue,
Marissa: something I've always wanted to ask.
Marissa: So they obviously get chippy on the
ice. They fight.
Marissa: Does that happen? Like if they're
fighting on the ice and then all of a
Marissa: sudden they're like shaking hands.
Yeah. Is there a lot of smack talk happening
on the ice?
You know, I think— I've always wanted to ask
this question.
Ryan: Yeah, that's something that on the ice,
it's like you're gonna go to battle
Ryan: and you need to try
to kill each other. But do you guys shit talk?
Yeah, oh, there's all kinds. Going through the
benches. Really? Yeah,
that's another thing which you gotta mic up
one of the players you can hear exactly.
I would love to because that's something we
obviously as fans, we can't hear anything.
Marissa: We can't see their mouths talking.
Obviously we can see them fighting.
Marissa: Maybe a little bit of, but I'm like,
are they actually talking shit?
Ryan: Yeah, there's a lot of, especially after
the whistles around the goaltender
Ryan: where they're in the scrums.
Marissa: That's where I feel like it always
happens.
Marissa: But then also they're like shaking
hands at the end of the game.
Yeah. So then the next game they're fighting.
Do you ever make up with a
Marissa: person? Did you ever get in a fight,
Ryan?
Ryan: [unclear] a few back in the day.
Marissa: Really? Did you ever make up with a
person?
Ryan: Yeah, because you play with them.
Marissa: That's what cracks me up about
hockey.
You could end up being on the same team as a
lot of these players because it
just, you go through— That's
what I'm always saying.
And there were players that I fought that,
yeah,
Ryan: I ended up playing with after. And I
think that's the [unclear] rule.
Ryan: That's like the beauty of hockey.
There's a line of respect.
Marissa: It literally cracks me up. I'm like,
Marissa: they were literally just fist
fighting. And then two minutes later,
Marissa: they're like shaking hands.
Ryan: Yeah, and that's competition. And that's
playing professional hockey.
Marissa: That's no other sport. No, because
usually— No other sport is allowed to
Marissa: fight like that. Or no other sport
like shake hands at the end of the game.
Ryan: Yeah. I've always— Just at the end of
the series, we're
Ryan: not every game they shake, they do the
handshake.
Ryan: It's just on the elimination games. But
still,
Ryan: that's when the emotions and everything
are at this
Ryan: highest level. And for them, they just
beat the shit out of each other.
Ryan: And then now they're gonna go on a line
and shake each other's hands.
Marissa: It's almost like a respect thing.
Like, yeah, we beat
Marissa: one extreme to the next.
Ryan: And then once they're off the ice, after
a series,
Ryan: they go and have dinner and have a beer
together.
Really? You're kidding. So maybe— I've always
wondered that.
Like if there's actual rivalry, rivalry?
Rivalry, yeah.
After or before a game, or if it's just on the
ice.
Marissa: Because it looks personal when they
go at it.
Ryan: There's players [unclear] incidents that
happen in games,
Ryan: because we play [unclear] so much. And
then later on,
Ryan: they're like— We're in a [unclear]
division.
Marissa: I'm going after you.
Ryan: Yeah, oh yeah, and they talk and just
say, heads up, and sure enough.
Really? Yeah.
Marissa: Even though they know they're gonna
get a penalty.
Oh yeah, they'll do what they need to do to, I
mean— That is so crazy.
It's all about winning, what it takes to win.
It's the damnest sport. It's so fun, and I
think the fights get the fans riled
[Music]